downloads-nl.net 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy for Downloads.nl

The privacy of our visitors to Downloads.nl is important to us. 

At Downloads.nl, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Downloads.nl, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language and the date and time of your request. The log files are kept for 30 days, after which they are deleted. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. 

We also use third party advertisements on Downloads.nl to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to Downloads.nl and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We've implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
